Sophie Engelbreth

Web Developer

Contact

Address

Rosklide, 84, 4000

Phone

29 66 77 50

E-mail

Sophieengelbreth@outlook.com

Skills

Web development projects

JavaScript

PHP

HTML

CSS

Idea brainstorming

Graphics design

Agile Workflow

UX Design

Software

Photoshop

Illustrator

InDesign

Word

WordPress

Languages

Danish

Engelish

Resourceful Front End Web Developer bringing in-depth knowledge of latest technology trends to produce clean website design. Experience handling complex HTML and CSS coding, design and extensions to meet organization's front-facing internet needs. Along with CSS and HTML knowledge, I have JavaScript experience along with some React.js, and PHP and Django programming.

Work History

2016-03 -2016-08

Dishwasher

Hotel Vin Huset, Næstved

- Stepped into additional roles during busy times to boost coverage of important stations.
- Assisted with kitchen prep work to help operations run smoothly and meet customer needs.
- Kept kitchen areas neat and clean by removing trash and organizing supplies.

2015-06 -2015-08

Waitress

Little Italy, Køge

- Maintained customer satisfaction with timely table check-ins to assess food and beverage needs.
- Greeted new customers, discussed specials, took drink orders and built immediate positive connections with guests.
- Folded napkins and prepared silverware sets to provide adequate supply for host station.
- Maintained order efficiency and accuracy through clear communication with kitchen staff, earning numerous recommendations from satisfied customers.

Education

2014-08 -2017-06 No Degree: Mat A, IT B, Progammering C

HTX Næstved - Næstved

2017-08 -2019-06

AP Degree: Multimedia Design

Copenhagen School Of Design And Technology (Kea)

- Copenhagen

2019-08 -Current Bachelor's in Web Development: Web Development

Copenhagen School Of Design And Technology (Kea) - Copenhagen

Interests

Drawing and painting

Writing



05.04.2019

Anbefaling.

Sophie har været beskæftiget her hos os, som multimediedesigner. Dette var som en del af Sophies afsluttende uddannelse.

Den primære arbejdsopgave har været at opbygge vores hjemmeside. Sophie har været en væsentlig medarbejder i denne proces, med video redigering, klipning, og indhold.

Sophie har arbejdet selvstændigt og pligtopfyldende. De arbejdsopgaver der er blevet stillet Sophie, har hun løst med stor loyalitet og ansvarlighed.

Ansættelsesperioden: Praktikperiode på 10 uger,

Vi medgiver Sophie vores bedste anbefaling og ønsker hende held og lykke fremover.

Med venlig hilsen BAASTRUP A/S

Hans Erlandsen